Guide to Major Figures in American Music
Major Figures in American Music
- Mimaroglu, Ilhan
  - Mimaro?lu, Ilhan, 1984 1986; OHV 273 a; Mimaroğlu, İlhan K. (İlhan Kemaleddin), 1926-2012; Approximate Running Time: 45 mins
    Mimaroğlu, İlhan K. (İlhan Kemaleddin), 1926-2012
- Mingus, Charles
  - Mingus, Charles, undated; OHV 88 a; Brower, William A.; Approximate Running Time: 42 mins; Transcript Page Count: 23 pages
    Mingus, Charles, 1922-1979
- Mingus, Sue
  - Mingus, Sue, 2017 March 6; OHV 88 b-c; Bendian, Gregg; Approximate Running Time: 105 mins
    Mingus, Sue
- Mitchell, Nicole
  - Mitchell, Nicole, 2012 June 3; OHV 425 a-b; Bynum, Taylor Ho (1975-); Approximate Running Time: 76 mins
    Mitchell, Nicole, 1967-
- Mobberly, James
  - Mobberley, James, 2002 October 17; OHV 557 a
    Mobberley, James (1954)
- Monk, Meredith
  - Monk, Meredith, 1990 May 24; OHV 8 a-f; Grimes, Ev; Approximate Running Time: 171 mins; Transcript Page Count: 107 pages
    Monk, Meredith (1942-11-20-)
  - Monk, Meredith, undated; OHV 8 g-h; Approximate Running Time: 26 mins
    WGBH Boston?
- Moog, Robert
  - Moog, Robert, 1979 February 1; OHV 213 a-c; Kretschmer, Joan Thomson; Approximate Running Time: 225 mins; Transcript Page Count: 54 pages
    Long Island, NY
    Moog, Bob
  - Moog, Robert, 1979 February 2; OHV 213 d-f
- Moore, Carman
  - Moore, Carman, undated; OHV 262 a; Friedner, Carl
    Moore, Carmen, 1972-
- Moore, Douglas
  - Moore, Douglas, 1968 November 23; OHV 305 a; Approximate Running Time: 16 mins
    Moore, Douglas
- Moore, Richard F.
  - Moore, Richard F., 1983 August 23; OHV 135 a-d; Plush, Vincent, 1950-; Transcript Page Count: 80 pages
    Moore, Richard, 1927-2009
- Moore, Robert
  - Moore, Robert, 1978 May 17; OHV 210 a; McTee, Cindy, 1953-; Approximate Running Time: 41 mins; Transcript Page Count: 18 pages
    Moore, Robert, 1932 September 20-
- Moore, Ted
  - Moore, Ted, 2023 April 13; OHV 578 a; 1 Computer File; 759 megabytes; Approximate running time: 75 mins
    Moore, Ted (Composer)
- Moran, Robert
  - Moran, Robert, 1983 October 29; OHV 153 a-f; Plush, Vincent, 1950-; Approximate Running Time: 212 mins; Transcript Page Count: 148 pages
    Moran, Robert F., Jr.
- Moran, Jason
  - Moran, Jason, 2012 October 22; OHV 434 a; Approximate Running Time: 80 mins
    Calhoun College Master's Tea
    Moran, Jason (1975-01-21-)
  - Moran, Jason, 2018 April 12; OHV 434 b; Approximate Running Time: 92 mins
    Black Sound and the Archive Working Group (BSAW) Workshop at Yale
  - Moran, Jason, 2018 April 12; OHV 434 c-d; Approximate Running Time: 76 mins
    Daphne Brooks and Brian Kane
- Moravec, Paul
  - Moravec, Paul, 2006 November 21; OHV 352 a-b; Mattis, Olivia; Approximate Running Time: 119 mins; Transcript Page Count: 49 pages
    Garden City, NY (Adelphi U)
    Moravec, Paul, 1957-
- Moross, Jerome
  - Moross, Jerome, circa 1967; OHV 371 a; Jory, Margaret, 1937-1985
    Moross, Jerome, 1913-1983
  - Moross, Jerome, undated; OHV v371 1
- Morton, Lawrence
  - Morton, Lawrence, 1966; OHV 58 a-i; Tusler, Adelaide G.; Transcript Page Count: 562 pages
    Morton, Lawrence, 1904-1987
- Mosko, Stephen
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1984 June 19; OHV 359 n; Approximate Running Time: 20 mins
    University of Southern California, concert in Sylmar, CA
    KUSC
    Mosko, Stephen L.
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 October 21; OHV 359 d
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 October 23; OHV 359 e
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 November 6; OHV 359 a
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 November 8; OHV 359 b
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 November 13; OHV 359 f
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 November 20; OHV 359 g
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 November 22; OHV 359 h
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 November 25; OHV 359 i
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 December 11; OHV 359 j
  - Mosco, Stephen, 1991 December 16; OHV 359 k
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 December 16; OHV 359 c
  - Mosko, Stephen, 1991 December 19; OHV 359 l
  - Mosko, Stephen, 2004 December 11; OHV 359 o-p; Knowles, Amy; Zuckman, Glen; Approximate Running Time: 91 mins
    Green Valley, CA
  - Mosko, Stephen, 2005 April 12; OHV 359 m; Mosko, Stephen L.; Approximate Running Time: 75 mins
- Muhly, Nico
  - Muhly, Nico, 2012 January 12; OHV 416 a-e; Raymond, Jenny; Approximate Running Time: 146 mins
    Muhly, Nico (19810826)
- Mumford, Jeffrey
  - Mumford, Jeffrey, 2012 January 26; OHV 418 a; Approximate Running Time: 28 mins
    Mumford, Jeffrey, 1955-
- Mumma, Gordon
  Mumma, Gordon, 1935-
  - Mumma, Gordon, 1983 May 17; OHV 125 a-f; Plush, Vincent, 1950-; Approximate Running Time: 277 mins; Transcript Page Count: 157 pages
    Santa Cruz, CA
- Murail, Tristan
  - Murail, Tristan, 2005 November 17; OHV 472 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 110 mins
    Murail, Tristan (1947-03-11-)
- Musgrave, Thea
  - Musgrave, Thea, 1983 May 12; OHV 122 a-d; Plush, Vincent, 1950-; Approximate Running Time: 164 mins; Transcript Page Count: 82 pages
    Musgrave, Thea (1928-05-27-)
- Nancarrow, Conlon
  - Nancarrow, Conlon, 1982 August 29; OHV 141 d; Plush, Vincent, 1950-; Approximate Running Time: 11 mins; Transcript Page Count: 7 pages
    Nancarrow, Conlon, 1912-1997
  - Nancarrow, Conlon, 1986 April 18; OHV 141 a-c; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 105 mins; Transcript Page Count: 57 pages
  - Nancarrow, Conlon, 1986 April 18; OHV 141 e; Sachs, Joel (19391219); Approximate Running Time: 13 mins
  - Nancarrow, Conlon, 1987 October 12; OHV 141 f; Duffie, Bruce; Approximate Running Time: 28 mins
  - Stephens, Luis, 2022 August 23; OHV 141 g; Greeson, James, 1951-; 1 Computer File; 649 megabytes; Approximate running time: 64 mins
    Fayettevill, AR
    Stephens, Luis; Nancarrow, Conlon, 1912-1997
- Nee, Thomas
  - Nee, Thomas, 1983 February 12; OHV 163 a-d; Plush, Vincent, 1950-; Approximate Running Time: 155 mins; Transcript Page Count: 58 pages
    Leucadia, CA
    Nee, Thomas
- Negrón, Angélica
  - Negrón, Angélica, 2023 August 21; OHV 583 a; Bendian, Gregg; 1 Computer File; 4.74 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 93 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Brooklyn, NY
    Negrón, Angélica, 1981-
- Newlin, Dixie
  Newlin, Dika
  - Newlin, Dixie, 1979 November 2; OHV 233 qqqqq-rrrrr; Olmstead, Andrea; Approximate Running Time: 77 mins
    Newlin, Dixie
- Newman, Thomas
  - Newman, Thomas, 2019 July 2; OHV 523 a; Approximate Running Time: 76 mins
    Newman, Thomas, 1955-
- Niblock, Phill
  - Niblock, Phill, 2023 Jun 8; OHV 581 a-c; Bendian, Gregg; 3 Computer Files; 2.67 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 83 mins
    Niblock, Phill, 1933
- Norman, Andrew
  - Norman, Andrew, 2013 January 4; OHV 436 a-c; Valenti, Maura; Approximate Running Time: 163 mins
    Norman, Andrew, 1979-
- North, Alex
  - North, Alex, 1963 April 7; OHV WQXR 2 d
    Crowther
    North, Alex (1910-12-04-1991-09-08)
  - North, Alex, 1980 March 20 1980 March 21; OHV 231 a-f; Raksin, David (1912-08-04-2004-08-09); Approximate Running Time: 179 mins; Transcript Page Count: 37 pages
- Nurock, Kirk
  - Nurock, Kirk, 2019 June 27; OHV 530 a-e; Bendian, Gregg; 5 Computer Files; 2.8 gigabytes; Approximate Running Time: 190 mins
    Nurock, Kirk
- O'Meara, Eva Judd
  - O'Meara, Eva Judd, 1969 June 27; OHV 26 a-c; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 97 mins; Transcript Page Count: 42 pages
    O'Meara, Eva Judd, 1884-1979
  - O'Meara, Eva Judd, 1973 January 24; OHV 26 d-e; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 65 mins
  - O'Meara, Eva Judd, undated; OHV 26 f; Perlis, Vivian
- Olivero, Betty
  - Olivero, Betty, 2002 October 31; OHV 325 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 132 mins
    Olivero, Betty, 1954-
- Oliveros, Pauline
  - Oliveros, Pauline, 1981 November 10; OHV 90 a-b; Oneppo, Martha; Approximate Running Time: 54 mins; Transcript Page Count: 19 pages
    Oliveros, Pauline, 1932-2016
  - Oliveros, Pauline, 1983 February 1; OHV 90 c-d; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 85 mins
  - Oliveros, Pauline, 1983 February 1; OHV v90 R1-2; Perlis, Vivian
  - Oliveros, Pauline, 1995 April 14; OHV 90 e; Donovan, Erin; Approximate Running Time: 34 mins; Transcript Page Count: 12 pages
    New York State
  - Oliveros, Pauline, 1998 June 8; OHV 90 f-k; Van Cleve, Libby; Approximate Running Time: 211 mins; Transcript Page Count: 77 pages
    Kingston, N.Y.
- Ono, Yoko
  - Ono, Yoko and Cage, John, 1983; OHV v41c; Perlis, Vivian; Transcript Page Count: 9 pages
    Ono, Yōko, 1933-; Cage, John, 1912-1992
- Oppens, Ursula
  - Oppens, Ursula, 2020 January 14; OHV 538 a-c; Bendian, Gregg; Approximate Running Time: 107 mins
    Oppens, Ursula, 1944-
- Ornstein, Leo
  Ornstein, Leo, 1892-2002
  - Ornstein, Leo and Pauline, 1972 December 8; OHV 21 a-d; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 127 mins; Transcript Page Count: 53 pages
    Waban, MA
    Ornstein, Leo, 1892-2002; Ornstein, Pauline
  - Ornstein, Pauline, 1972 December 8; OHV 21 d; Perlis, Vivian; Transcript Page Count: 35-53 pages
    Ornstein, Pauline
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1976 December 11; OHV 21 m; Approximate Running Time: 37 mins
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1977 November 19; OHV 21 g-l; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 482 mins; Transcript Page Count: 81 pages
    Brownsville, TX
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1977 November 20; OHV v21 R1-8; Perlis, Vivian
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1983 June 15; OHV 21 n-o; O'Grady, Terence J.; Approximate Running Time: 43 mins
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1987; OHV v21b R9-10
    St. Norbert College, De Pere, WI
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1987 December 1; OHV v21a R1-3
    Green Bay, WI
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1987 December 4; OHV 21 p-q; Approximate Running Time: 45 mins
    DePere, WI
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1987 December 4; OHV 21 r-s; Approximate Running Time: 67 mins
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1987 December 4; OHV 21 t-u; Approximate Running Time: 54 mins
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1987 December 4; OHV 21 v-w; Ornstein, Severo M.; Westney, William (19470214); Approximate Running Time: 49 mins
    De Pere, WI
    Jan Weller, Severo Ornstein, William Westney
  - Ornstein, Leo, undated; OHV 21 e-f
  - Trachtenberg, Betty, 1993 April 27; OHV 21 x; Penner, Judith, 1945-
- Osby, Greg
  - Osby, Greg, 2018 May 11; OHV 513 a-d; Bendian, Gregg; Approximate Running Time: 102 mins
    Cherry Hill, NJ
    Osby, Greg (1960-08-03-)
- Oteri, Frank J.
  - Oteri, Frank J., 2013 February 28; OHV 440 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 161 mins
    Oteri, Frank J., 1964-
- Owens, Jimmy
  - Owens, Jimmy, 2018 November 23; OHV 521 a-d; Bendian, Gregg; Approximate Running Time: 190 mins
    Owens, Jimmy, 1943-
- Palestine, Charlemagne
  - Palestine, Charlemagne, 1974; OHV 477 a-b; Marshall, Ingram, 1942-; Approximate Running Time: 59 mins
    Palestine, Charlemagne
  - Palestine, Charlemagne, 2015 March 8; OHV 477 c-d; Marshall, Ingram, 1942-; Approximate Running Time: 124 mins
- Panetti, Joan
  - Panetti, Joan, 2010 March 1; OHV 397 a-b; Van Cleve, Libby; Approximate Running Time: 148 mins; Transcript Page Count: 84 pages
    Panetti, Joan
- Parisot, Aldo
  - Parisot, Aldo, 2007 October 19; OHV 384 a-b; Hawkshaw, Susan, (Musicologist); Transcript Page Count: 267 pages
    Yale School of Music
    Parisot, Aldo, 1921-
  - Parisot, Aldo, 2007 October 26; OHV 384 c-d
  - Parisot, Aldo, 2007 November 2; OHV 384 e-f
  - Parisot, Aldo, 2007 November 16; OHV 384 g-h
- Parisot, Elizabeth
  - Parisot, Elizabeth, 2008 February 29; OHV 389 a; Hawkshaw, Susan, (Musicologist); Approximate Running Time: 79 mins; Transcript Page Count: 66 pages
    Sawyer Parisot, Elizabeth
  - Parisot, Elizabeth, 2008 June 5; OHV 389 b-c; Hawkshaw, Susan, (Musicologist); Approximate Running Time: 149 mins; Transcript Page Count: 105 pages
- Partch, Harry
  - Partch, Harry, 1953 November 19 1954; OHV 24 h; Approximate Running Time: 19 mins
    Berkeley, CA/KPFA
    Partch, Harry, 1901-1974
  - Partch, Harry, 1974 March 1; OHV 24 a-f; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 258 mins; Transcript Page Count: 76 pages
  - Partch, Harry, undated; OHV 24 g
  - Partch, Harry, undated; OHV 24 i-j; Approximate Running Time: 49 mins
- Paul, Les
  - Paul, Les, 1978 April 3; OHV 207 a-n, p-z2; Kretschmer, Joan Thomson; Approximate Running Time: 1024 mins; Transcript Page Count: 85 pages
    Mahwah, NJ
    Paul, Les (1915-06-09-2009-08-11)
  - Paul, Les, 1978 June 16; OHV 207 aa-bb; Kretschmer, Joan Thomson; Approximate Running Time: 78 mins; Transcript Page Count: 23 pages
- Paulus, Stephen
  - Paulus, Stephen, 1994 March 8; OHV 240 a-c; Van Cleve, Libby; Approximate Running Time: 113 mins; Transcript Page Count: 49 pages
    Paulus, Stephen
- Pavone, Mario
  - Pavone, Mario, 2018 July 11; OHV 516 a-b; Testa, Carl (1984-); Approximate Running Time: 125 mins
    Prospect, CT
    Pavone, Mario, 1941-
- Peacock, Gary
  - Peacock, Gary, 2013 September 20; OHV 455 a-f; Approximate Running Time: 214 mins; Transcript Page Count: 77 pages
    Claryville, NY
- Penderecki, Krzysztof
  - Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1986 January 27; OHV 355 b-c
    Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1933-
  - Penderecki, Krzysztof, 1995 March 21; OHV 355 d-e
  - Penderecki, Krzysztof, 2000 March 9; OHV 355 a; Approximate Running Time: 39 mins
    Bruce Duffie
  - Penderecki, Krzysztof, 2005 April 21; OHV 355 f
- Perez, Danilo
  - Perez, Danilo, 2013 August 24; OHV 457 a-f; Approximate Running Time: 255 mins; Transcript Page Count: 99 pages
    Quincy, MA
- Perle, George
  - Perle, George, 1985 April 13; OHV 170 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 180 mins
    Christopher Hailey
  - Perle, George, 1985 April 23; OHV 170 e-i; Approximate Running Time: 229 mins
  - Perle, George, 1985 April 29; OHV 170 j-n; Approximate Running Time: 220 mins
  - Perle, George, 1985 November 15; OHV 170 o-q; Approximate Running Time: 123 mins; Transcript Page Count: 69 pages
  - Perle, George, 1986 January 24; OHV 170 r-t; Approximate Running Time: 116 mins; Transcript Page Count: 225 pages
  - Perle, George, 1986 May 20; OHV 170 u; Approximate Running Time: 41 mins
- Perlis, Vivian
  - Perlis, Vivian, 1998 July 9; OHV 287 a-c; Transcript Page Count: 62 pages
  - Perlis, Vivian, 1998 July 14; OHV 287 d-f
  - Perlis, Vivian, 1999 July 7; OHV 287 g-h
  - Perlis, Vivian, 2007 July 18; OHV 287 i-k; Approximate Running Time: 168 mins
  - Perlis, Vivian, 2014 June 30; OHV 287 l-q; Approximate Running Time: 116 mins; Transcript Page Count: 37 pages
  - Perlis, Vivian, 2017 January 13; OHV 287 r
    Lou Brouwers
- Persichetti, Vincent
  - Persichetti, Vincent, 1984 May 10; OHV 164 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 126 mins; Transcript Page Count: 64 pages
    Janice Fournier
  - Persichetti, Vincent, 1984 September 25; OHV 164 d-e; Approximate Running Time: 31 mins; Transcript Page Count: 8 pages
    Ev Grimes
  - Persichetti, Vincent, 1986 November 15; OHV 164 g; Approximate Running Time: 60 mins
  - Persichetti, Vincent, 1987 May 12; OHV 164 f; Approximate Running Time: 46 mins
- Peterson, Anne (Capen) and Wigmore, Viola Pearl (Holmes)
  - Peterson, Anne (Capen) and Wigmore, Viola Pearl (Holmes), 1980 October 20; OHV 87 a
    Manomet, MA
    Roger L. Hall
- Picker, Tobias
  - Picker, Tobias, 2016 March 30; OHV 488 a-c; Picker, Tobias, 1954-; Bendian, Gregg; Approximate Running Time: 155 mins
    Location of Interview
    Staatsburg, NY
- Pinkham, Daniel
  - Pinkham, Daniel, 2001 November 17; OHV 321 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 157 mins; Transcript Page Count: 50 pages
    Elizabeth Crouch Fitts
- Pintscher, Matthias
  - Pintscher, Matthias, 2011 October 27; OHV 415 a; Approximate Running Time: 99 mins
- Pisk, Paul
  - Pisk, Paul, 1983 May 10; OHV 121 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 167 mins; Transcript Page Count: 71 pages
    Hollywood, CA
- Piston, Walter
  - Piston, Walter, circa 1967; OHV 372 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 41 mins; Transcript Page Count: 16 pages
    Margaret Jory
- Pollard, Mark
  - Pollard, Mark, 2016 October 13; OHV 492 a-d
- Porter, Quincy
  - Brown, Lois, 1972 October 11; OHV 17 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 159 mins; Transcript Page Count: 91 pages
    Caitriona Bolster
  - Simonds, Bruce, 1972 November 16; OHV 17 f-g; Approximate Running Time: 63 mins; Transcript Page Count: 39 pages
  - Wilson, Keith, 1972 October 31; OHV 17 h-i; Approximate Running Time: 43 mins; Transcript Page Count: 26 pages
  - Brown, Lois, 1972 October 18; OHV 17 d-e
- Potter, Chris
  - Potter, Chris, 2013 September 4; OHV 458 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 129 mins
- Powell, Mel
  - Powell, Mel, 1983 May 13; OHV 123 a-f; Approximate Running Time: 248 mins; Transcript Page Count: 125 pages
    Van Nuys, CA
  - Powell, Mel, 1983 September 1; OHV 123 g-dd; Approximate Running Time: 958 mins
  - Powell, Mel, 1984 October 1; OHV 123 ee-hh; Approximate Running Time: 191 mins
  - Powell, Mell /Mosko, Lucky, 1993 October 1; OHV 123 ll-mm; Approximate Running Time: 105 mins
  - Powell, Mel, 1997 December 11; OHV 123 ii-kk; Approximate Running Time: 115 mins; Transcript Page Count: 42 pages
    Sherman Oaks, CA
- Preston, Don
  - Preston, Don, 2013 March 20; OHV 449 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 120 mins
- Price, Florence
  - Brown, Rae Linda, 2014 June 4; OHV 572 a; Greeson, James, 1951-; 1 Computer File; 954 megabytes; Approximate running time: 87 mins
    Interview conducted in Fayetteville, AR, for James Greeson's 2015 documentary, "The Caged Bird: The Live and Music of Florence B. Price"
    Brown, Rae Linda, 1953-2017; Price, Florence, 1887-1953
  - Dillard, Tom and Nutt, Tim, undated; OHV 572 c; Dillard, Tom W.; Nutt, Timothy G.; 1 Computer File; 31.7 megabytes; Approximate running time: 56 mins
    A talk on the music of Florence Price, presented at the University of Arkansas in Fayetteville, AR and used in James Greeson's 2015 documentary, "The Caged Bird: The Live and Music of Florence B. Price"
    Price, Florence, 1887-1953
  - Heard, Richard, 2014 July 31; OHV 572 d; Greeson, James, 1951-; 1 Computer File; 317 megabytes; Approximate running time: 14 mins
    Interview conducted in Winston-Salem, NC, for James Greeson's 2015 documentary, "The Caged Bird: The Live and Music of Florence B. Price"
    Heard, Richard Earl; Price, Florence, 1887-1953
  - Jackson, Barbara Garvey, 2014 August 18; OHV 572 e; Greeson, James, 1951-; 1 Computer File; 685 megabytes; Approximate running time: 31 mins
    Jackson, Barbara Garvey (19290927); Price, Florence, 1887-1953
  - Johnson, Calvert, 2014 August 1; OHV 572 b; Greeson, James, 1951-; 1 Computer File; 393 megabytes; Approximate running time: 18 mins
    Interview conducted in Atlanta, GA, for James Greeson's 2015 documentary, "The Caged Bird: The Live and Music of Florence B. Price"
    Johnson, Calvert, 1949-; Price, Florence, 1887-1953
  - Phibbs, Morris, 2014 July 14; OHV 572 f; 1 Computer File; 786 megabytes; Approximate running time: 36 mins
    Interview conducted in Chicago, IL, for James Greeson's 2015 documentary, "The Caged Bird: The Live and Music of Florence B. Price"
    Phibbs, Morris A. (Morris Allen), 1951-; Price, Florence, 1887-1953
- Puts, Kevin
  - Puts, Kevin, 2021 May 25; OHV 547 a; Bendian, Gregg; 1 Computer File; 980 megabytes; Approximate running time: 115 mins
    Interview recorded via videochat, with interviewee in Yonkers, NY and interviewer in Fair Lawn, NJ
    Puts, Kevin (1972-01-03-)
  - Puts, Kevin, 2021 June 8; OHV 547 b; Bendian, Gregg; 1 Computer File; 1.45 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 75 mins
- Radzynski, Jan
  - Radzynski, Jan, 2003 February 6; OHV 558 a
    Radzynski, Jan (19500618)
- Rakowski, David
  - Rakowski, David, 2014 April 3; OHV 466 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 62 mins
- Raksin, David
  - Raksin, David, 1976 December 6; OHV 226 a-g; Approximate Running Time: 881 mins; Transcript Page Count: 453 pages
    CA
    Irene Kahn Atkins
    Part g ends with beginning of next interview (OHV 226 g-n).
  - Raksin, David, 1977 February 15; OHV 226 g-n
    Part 6 begins with end of previoud interview (OHV 226 a-g).
  - Raksin, David, 1996 August 22; OHV 226 o-p; Approximate Running Time: 150 mins; Transcript Page Count: 57 pages
    Jon Newsom
  - Raksin, David, 1995 August 24; OHV 226 q-r
- Rands, Bernard
  - Rands, Bernard, 1987 May 11; OHV 193 a-h; Approximate Running Time: 228 mins; Transcript Page Count: 113 pages
  - Rands, Bernard, 2009 October 8; OHV 193 i; Approximate Running Time: 54 mins
- Read, Gardner
  - Read, Gardner, 1959 April 5; 1980 April 10; OHV 291 a; Approximate Running Time: 49 mins
    Boston, MA/Cleveland, OH
    Kenneth Beene, Klaus Roy
  - Read, Gardner, 1959 May; OHV 291 b; Approximate Running Time: 47 mins
    Manchester, MA/Boston, MA
    Mary Ann Dood, Jules Wolffers
- Reich, Steve
  - Reich, Steve, 1978 May 25; OHV 186 o; Approximate Running Time: 10 mins
  - Reich, Steve, 1981 May 19; OHV 186 n; Approximate Running Time: 13 mins
  - Reich, Steve, 1985 June 19; OHV 186 aa; Approximate Running Time: 53 mins
  - Reich, Steve, 1986 December 15 1986 December 16; OHV 186 a-i; Approximate Running Time: 233 mins; Transcript Page Count: 138 pages
  - Reich, Steve, 1987; OHV 186 m; Approximate Running Time: 29 mins
    John Shafer - Americathon
  - Reich, Steve, 1990 January 17; OHV 186 j-k; Transcript Page Count: 55* pages
    Dorothy Horowitz
  - Reich, Steve, 1996 June 21; OHV 186 l; Approximate Running Time: 10 mins; Transcript Page Count: 6 pages
  - Reich, Steve, 2001 January 18; OHV 186 p-q; Approximate Running Time: 72 mins
  - Reich, Steve, 2002 August 2; OHV 186 r-t; Approximate Running Time: 123 mins; Transcript Page Count: 81 pages
    Rochester, VT
  - Reich, Steve, 2002 October 12; OHV 186 u-v; Transcript Page Count: 28 pages
    New York, telephone from VT
    Rebecca Kim
  - Reich, Steve, 2012 March 29; OHV 186 bb; Approximate Running Time: 62 mins
  - Reich, Steve, 2016 July 11; OHV 186 cc-ff; Approximate Running Time: 149 mins
    Pound Ridge, NY
  - Reich, Steve, undated; OHV 186 y-z; Approximate Running Time: 78 mins
  - Reich, Steve, 2002 October 25; OHV 186 w-x
- Reis, Claire
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 January 21; OHV 22 a-c; Transcript Page Count: 302 pages
    Part a of this interview is restricted. Access may be granted to a patron who has obtained direct permission from the interviewee or their estate.
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 January 29; OHV 22 d-e
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 February 5; OHV 22 f-h
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 February 18; OHV 22 i-j
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 February 26; OHV 22 k-m
    Part m ends with beginning of next interview (OHV 22 m-p)
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 March 3; OHV 22 m-p
    Part m begins with the last part of the previous interview (OHV 22 k-m)
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 April 1; OHV 22 q-r
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 April 7; OHV 22 s
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 May 26; OHV 22 t-u
  - Reis, Claire, 1976 July 15; OHV 22 v-w
  - Reis, Claire, 1977 January 28; OHV 22 x-y
  - Reis, Claire, 1977 May 6; OHV 22 z
  - Reis, Claire, 1977 July 9; OHV v22 R1-3
- Reynolds, Roger
  - Reynolds, Roger, 1983 March 1; OHV 113 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 179 mins; Transcript Page Count: 88 pages
    Del Mar, CA
- Richter, Marga
  - Richter, Marga, 1975 July 9; OHV 51 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 198 mins; Transcript Page Count: 106 pages
    Frances Harmeyer
- Rieti, Vittorio
  - Rieti, Vittorio, 1981 August 17; OHV 85 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 94 mins; Transcript Page Count: 37 pages
    Mark Carrington
- Riley, Terry
  - Riley, Terry, 1997 June 17; OHV 251 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 162 mins; Transcript Page Count: 84 pages
    Camptonville, CA
- Roach, Max
  - Roach, Max, 1997 December 20; OHV 272 a; Approximate Running Time: 43 mins
    Kay Roberts
- Robb, John Donald
  - Robb, John Donald, 1983 July 23; OHV 131 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 63 mins; Transcript Page Count: 26 pages
    Shelter Island, NY
- Rochberg, George
  - Rochberg, George, 1983 October 12; OHV 150 a-e; Approximate Running Time: 200 mins; Transcript Page Count: 91 pages
    Newtown Square, PA
  - Rochberg, George, 1985 January 31; OHV 150 l; Approximate Running Time: 57 mins
  - Rochberg, George, 1986 March 11; OHV 150 m; Approximate Running Time: 30 mins